Power. Justice. Darkness. Light.
Double Dragon is a action, adventure, comedy film directed by James Yukich.
Two brothers have half of a powerful ancient Chinese talisman.
An evil gang leader has the other half, and determines to get the brothers'
half and have a complete medallion so he can gain absolute power.
Jimmy Lee, played by Mark Dacascos.
Billy Lee, played by Scott Wolf.
Kongo Shuko, played by Robert Patrick.
Linda Lash, played by Kristina Wagner.
Satori Imada, played by Julia Nickson.
Marian Delario, played by Alyssa Milano.
Double Dragon is a 1994 American martial arts film, based
on the video game series of the same name.
The film was directed by James Yukich, whose previous credits include the
Genesis music videos "That's All" and "Invisible Touch".
Starring Mark Dacascos and Scott Wolf as brothers Jimmy and Billy Lee, along with Alyssa Milano as Marian Delario and Robert Patrick as antagonist Koga Shuko, the
plot takes place in an earthquake-crippled Los Angeles in 2007; the city is styled as a mix between a post-apocalyptic and 80s/90s punk environment.
It failed both critically and financially, receiving generally mixed reviews, with praise for its
special effects and action sequences, but criticism for its writing and performances.
The film explores themes of martial arts, street gang,
mutant, post-apocalyptic future, earthquake.
The tone is lighthearted and thought_provoking.